Rehan Willemse

90 Steve Biko street · Potchefstroom · 2531 rehan.willemse@gmail.com · 079 696 7053 ·

Personal Statement

I am a hardworking individual that performs well under pressure and I learn very fast, I love new experiences and have learnt a lot of team based skills during my education at university, I am also very independent and responsible.

Education and Qualifications

NWU Potchefstroom (2014 – 2019) (2020 - 2021 part time)

- Bsc Information Technology
- VBA, C#, Calculus, Algebra, Databases (MySQL), Chemistry, Physics,
 Computer Assisted Drawing, Discrete Mathematics, Linear programming

High school Secunda (1 January 2009 – 31 December 2013)

■ Matriculated – Mathematics

Natural Sciences

Biology

Accounting

Life Sciences

Afrikaans

English

HyperionDev (Jan 2021)

- Software Engineering Bootcamp
- Python
- Java
- CSS overview
- HTML overview
- Machine Learning introduction
- JDBC introduction

Below is a link to my HyperionDev portfolio https://www.hyperiondev.com/portfolio/54250/

Employment History

Waiter [2010 - 2013]

Maretha Marx Catering

Duties: client care

Bar Manager [2015 - 2016]

Potchefstroom Country Club Duties: Stock take, Cash Up, Stock ordering, Bank deposits, Employee management, customer care

Main Achievements

C# Project [2018 - 2018]

 Created an app that had to be able to login to an account with verification and security checks.

Database Project [2018 - 2018]

Created a fully functioning database and front-end GUI for the South African Hunting Union to keep track of members, registrations, sales and stock, with a live update function for a scoreboard and charts to show member activity and event participations. This was a very successful team project, we were approached by the hunting union asking if we would like to sell them the program, but with strict rules of the university we decided to decline that offer.

Selective Interests

 Playing around on development software, Socialising with friends (online or in person), Playing games with friends, playing sports (golf), Fishing and Camping.

Other

South African driving licence code EB.

References available upon request.